This is a one-in-100,000 chance of
happening. This has a one-in-1 million
chance of happening. This has a one-in-1
billion chance of happening. That's just
not possible. We're going to be reacting
to the most improbable things that have
ever happened. Being ambidextrous,
one-in-100 odds.
I had a kid when my K5 class that was
ambidextrous, and I thought it was so
cool. One-in-100 odds means only 1% of
people can do this.
Well, that would explain it cuz I know
that one kid, and I know about 99 other
people, so that makes sense.
Now, we're going to jump up to
one-in-750
odds, which is having 12 fingers. What?
That's genius to play guitar. Like, that
would be really helpful. That's so cool.
One-in-750, that's a lot more people
than I thought. Walt? Yeah? How many
people in the world have 12 fingers? 7
and 1/2 million.
Wow. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
That means there's 15 million extra
fingers on the planet. And they're just
out there wiggling around. All right,
double egg yolk.
Wait, okay, why was this guy recording
himself with cracking eggs?
Was he going for this?
He knew. He knew. Double.
Oh, he got the booby egg. Seeing a 360
rainbow. What does that even mean? Oh,
that's what you mean. It's basically
like looking through a camera lens
almost. That's crazy.
a little portal.
That's how Doctor Strange be getting
around. Raining red rain.
What does that mean?
There's something very out of the
ordinary about this rain. It's blood
red. Why? Tell us. Why is it red? We
need TO KNOW.
WHY? THIS IS NO SCIENCE fiction story.
Okay.
Okay. It's weather right here on Earth.
We get that. They didn't even tell us.
Wow.
No way. Living to 100 is one-in-3,700
odds.
Wow, she looks good for 104.
Hey, maybe you hit her up. She
Well, I have a girlfriend, but if I
didn't I would. Two doctors have told me
that if I drink it I will die, but they
died first.
Yo. Yo. Granny just popped off. Seeing a
reverse tiger. It's just walking
backwards. Oh, it's it's like a black
tiger with orange stripes instead of
orange tiger with black stripes.
That's cool.
Do you think like animals in the wild
are like, "Whoa, he dripped out." Or do
are they like different shun? Seeing how
he was alone, probably the latter.
I don't know why he'd need a ladder. He
has claws to climb up trees.
He was struggling. The ladder would have
made it quicker. Scoring a perfect
bowling game.
Wow, one-in-11,000, really? I think the
higher odds are scoring a perfect
bowling game and then going and getting
a kiss from a female. I was thinking the
same thing. Yeah, it's just the shoes.
Any sport that you can eat and you have
to wear goofy ass shoes, you're it's
just I'm not going to take it serious.
I'm sorry. Finding a giant amethyst.
What's an amethyst?
It's a gem. Oh, it's Logan Paul.
Wait, do you think he'll find a zoo in
there?
OH MY GOD. WHOA, CLASSIC Logan Paul
face. Oh my god, I haven't seen that
forever. Look at that face.
like one of our main channel thumbnails.
But ours are ironic, so it's okay.
Was that fake or was that real? It
looked real. That is beautiful.
There's a one-in-25,000 chance that your
cat gets four ears.
Oh, I love it.
I wonder if it does better in the wild.
It would do better in my home.
Why is your tongue out? Cuz it's not
just enough for it to have four ears. It
also has to just be like "Bleah."
Finding a puffy Dorito. How do you
measure that this is one-in-200,000?
Uh how do you measure what is a puffy
Dorito? Like, how puffy does it have to
be to be a puffy Dorito?
Like, do you just open up 200,000 bags
of Doritos and go, "Oh, that's how long
it took to find one." Man, it just made
this 13-year-old $20,000 richer. See,
here's the difference between me and
your average person. Wouldn't have
thought twice.
You would have ate it.
Ate it so quick. Here's what would have
happened in my head. I would have been
like, "Holy crap, this looks like it's
going to taste better than normal."
And guess what?
What?
It's why snacking hasn't made you 20
grand.
It's fair. Flying through a lightning
storm. Yeah, flying through a lightning
storm something, but have you found a
puffy Dorito?
Pilots probably see that all the time.
Is that what they actually see?
I can't believe pilots actually have to
deal with that. That's crazy.
You know what's crazier? This package I
got for Chris.
Oh, sweet, it's finally here. What is
it?
Oh, I don't know. I order a lot of stuff
online. Oh, look, it's my official
Furby.
How many of those do you own?
Hundreds.
You should probably sell some of them.
I'm sure they're worth money.
And then I'll ship them.
How do I sell them, Jimothy? Shopify,
the sponsor of this video.
What's Shopify? I just ship packages.
Shopify offers an easy-to-use commerce
platform that makes starting a business
incredibly easy. So easy, in fact, that
even Chris could do it.
Yeah, and I'm stupid.
It can even help you grow your business
from selling one Furby a month to
selling billions of Furbies a month with
tools that are typically only available
for giant businesses. Wow, better get to
Furbing. Anyone can now create the
business of their dreams using Shopify.
Just click the link in the description
or go to this URL right here,
shopify.com/mrbeast.
Can I leave now? Two-headed lizard.
Oh my gosh. What are the odds of this?
One-in-500,000. Oh. That is sick
looking. Do you think they operate under
the same belly and same like poo poo? Do
you think one gets full when the other
one eats? He's like, "Yo, slow down."
I'm trying to enjoy this snack, too.
Fishing a blue lobster.
I saw this on TikTok.
What does he do at the end?
Fun lobster fact.
Lobsters can theoretically live
indefinitely as long as they can keep
molting their shell.
Why am I not a lobster?
Cuz you can't molt.
Accent changing syndrome.
Wait, Chris suffers from this?
What?
Lisa Alamia. Oh, no, from England,
sorry. is 100% Texan. Jeez, no way. I
Where are you from? From Rosenberg. Oh,
you Where is Where is that? I'm like,
"We're here in Rosenberg." Oh, you're
from here. How do you talk like that?
I've never heard of this in my entire
life. I don't have any earbuds in.
I I can't hear anything.
Raining in single spot. It was only
raining in this one spot on the street
and nowhere else in the city. Somebody's
pouring something.
Yeah, that's the cloud from cartoons
when you're sad.
Yeah, this person filming should have
just put the camera down and been like,
Giving birth to nine twins.
So, nine twins is that mean 18 kids or
She had nine kids at the same time.
Someone look at that man. That man got
something going on. You're the dad,
you're just like,
That is wild. She passed all nine of
those kids through her body. Do you
think the doctor pulled it out and said,
"Package delivery?" Could you imagine if
you had eight other Tuckers? Yeah, I'd
be tired. You'd be tuckered out. Finding
buried treasure.
One-in-2250
million.
A Northern California couple says they
were What does this deer have to do with
it?
when they saw an old tin can poking out
of the ground.
This guy looks like he pokes old tin
cans.
look like if he found a tin can he'd be
like, "I got to dig that up." No, grab a
stick. Did you know that there's no uh
recorded proof that a pirate has ever
buried treasure? Carl, shut up. No need
to ruin our fun. I just deliver
packages. Finding a perfect
doppelganger. One-in-900 million odds.
One wedding photographer got the
surprise of his life when he met his
doppelganger on a plane. That's crazy,
though. Look at that guy. He's like,
"Ha." He's like, "I'm a part of this. My
name's Bill. I'm a I was here."
A friend of Neil's shared the
doppelganger's picture on Twitter, and
it has been retweeted thousands of
times.
Thousands of times. 6,000 times. He's
breaking the internet. Winning the game
show Who Wants to Be a Millionaire.
One-in-a-billion. Really? I like to call
my parents right now. What a nerd. I
don't really need your help. I just
wanted to let you know that I'm going to
win the million dollars.
Richard Nixon, that's my final answer.
He's won a million dollars.
Whoa,
not only did he win a million dollars,
he got that rizz. What a chad. This next
person has 200 IQ.
His IQ is so big he can't have sleeves
on his shirt.
Most of us have an IQ of 100. 195 to
200, well, you're talking
one-in-several-billion
people. Oh, wow.
I didn't know how rare I was.
Yeah, same. That's crazy. That's 200. I
have a 206, so that's crazy. Wow, so
basically everyone in the world with
over 200 is in this room. That's crazy,
actually.
Galileo, 185. Isaac Newton, 190. And
Carl Jenkins. Wang can possibly be the
smartest person in the world.
And he uses that talent to pet horses.
Wait, I want you guys to look at this
number. Perfect NCAA March Madness
bracket. I'm not even going to say that
number. That's a lot of numbers. Nine
lots of numbers odds. Did somebody do
it?
I had the best bracket out of 11.57
million people. What was your strategy
for success? Well, I just filled out how
who I think is going to win.
The secret to success is luck. Subscribe
or you won't have any.
And I'll ship them.